## Narciso Braga Benigno

### Software developer

Last update: April 12, 2023

Up-to-date version of CV is available at <a href="https://narcisobenigno.github.io/cv">https://narcisobenigno.github.io/cv</a>

I've been developing software since 2007. Through those years, I have worked with multiple platforms such as Golang, Java, Ruby, Javascript and Kotlin. Along with on-premise and cloud solutions (AWS).

The more I develop software and read and understand its aspects, it's getting clear that the outcome is highly dependent on human interactions. Agile, at its roots, tries to address those aspects, bringing people together to collaborate, removing intermediaries and involving whoever is required to produce solutions and understand the emerging problems of a given product.

Therefore, I am still very excited about technology, but using more and more Lean, Flow and Agile principles. As well as practices such as TDD, Continuous Delivery, Continuous Integration, inception, prioritisation and clean code. This means: doing a small thing, delivering, measuring and refining, supported by technology and at a sustainable pace.

## **Professional Experience**

August 2020 - Present

### Indebted - Software developer - Sydney, Australia

InDebted is a debt collection company that relies a lot on data to provide a smarter and more sensible approach, supporting customers to get their financial life back on track. We support those purposes using an event-sourcing based system, techniques like DDD and TDD.



December 2018 - August 2020

### Pragmateam - Software developer - Sydney, Australia

Consultant software engineer helping clients to improve their technical and lean/XP skills. Furthermore, I'm working with technologies such as React, Kotlin and microservices as well as techniques as TDD, DDD, continuous delivery and inceptions.



July 2017 - September 2018

#### Bionexo - Software developer - São Paulo, Brazil

I have worked within the legacy platform team, helping the team apply techniques described in the book "Working Effectively with Legacy Code". So, we introduced automated tests and improved the code base quality and solving problems which were on the platform for years long and improving users satisfaction. Furthermore, I was involved in the project to migrate from that legacy platform to a new one.



### Education

# **Additional Experience**

## ThoughtWorks - Software Developer - São Paulo, Brazil

I worked as a consultant embedded to the customer's office, influencing, and helping them to improve their agile process, implementing continuous-delivery, and coding skills.

